三号收银台  查下价
Price check, register three.
他们在茧里  醒来时
They're in this cocoon, but they wake up
-一切混沌有如原生汤...  -原生汤  我知道
- and it's like a primordial soup. - Soup, I know.
-嘴跟屁股颠倒了  -别说了
- And their mouth is the butt... and the butt's the mouth, which is...  - Please stop....
我知道  我都知道了
I know. I already know!
我就是不想再听一遍  恕我直言
I just don't want to hear it again, no offense.
说得我都烦了
I..., you're driving me nuts.
我太兴奋了
I'm excited!
我从没去过豪宅
I've never been to a mansion before!
我不是去探亲  懂吗
Well, it's not a social visit, all right?
我姐特别讨厌
My sister sucks.
别这样  怎么说也是你姐
Hey, okay. That's your sister.
-你还看不起你姐呢  -是
- Yeah, you despise your sister.- Yeah, well,
因为我姐穷个叮当响
'cause my sister's a locksmith.
蜗居一族
She lives in a box.
你姐可是个大款
Your sister's a freakin' millionaire.
她才不是  她是嫁了个大款
Well, no, she married a millionaire;
区别大着呢
there's a big difference.
这豪宅真是富得流油啊
Baby got a big old butt!
-那是汽油  -什么
- That's gasoline. - What?
天呐  怎么会是汽油
My God! Why do you have gasoline?
我这叫省钱有道
Well, I'm not gonna pay Greenwich prices.
-那就把气油装在果汁瓶里吗  -是啊
- So you keep it in a juice jug?! - Yeah.
你喷得前面都是油
You spit all over my dash.
那你想让我怎么样
What'd you want me to do with it?
谁知道  就...
I don't know, deal with...
来了  警察  警察
here we go. Cop, cop, cop!
-把汽油藏起来  -为什么
- Put the gas away. - Why?
我能搞定
I got this.
-为什么  -我能搞定
- Why, why? - I got you, I got you.
你们好  没什么事吧
Howdy. Everything okay here?
-原来是个保安  -没事
- Security. - Yeah.
我们没事  也用不着你管
Yeah. We're fine, not that it's any of your concern.
-你们迷路了吗  -没有
- You guys lost? - No.
我姐住在这里
My sister lives here.
好吧  别惹乱子
Okay. Stay out of trouble.
遵命  「长官」
Will do, Officer.
什么情况  看不起穷人呗
What the hell was that? Guy treats us like a bunch of lowlifes?
格林威治的人就这个德行
Yeah, welcome to Greenwich.
我该朝他吐口痰
Yeah, I should have spit on him.
杰米  你上哪儿
Jimmy, where you going?
去野餐烧烤宴啊
To the barbecue.
不  你不跟我一起去
No. No, you're not coming in with me.
为什么呢
Why not?
因为你让我觉得丢脸
'Cause your embarrassing. You embarrass me.
你层次太低了呗
I'm embarrassed of you.
那我大老远从罗得岛开过来干什么
Then why the hell did I just drive up here from Rhode Island?
不开车  我就能喝酒啊
So I can drink.
听下比赛吧
Just pop on the game.
不  我不会就傻坐在这里...
No! I'm not gonna sit out here like some goon and...
-行  你走吧  走吧  -要投了
- Whoa, ninth, go, go. - Here comes the pitch.
-第一击  -都给我安静
- Called strike one. - Everyone, shut up.
好好打啊
Swing at crap!
-能给我一支烟吗  -不行
- Can I bum a smoke, please? - No.
好吧  算你狠  给你一块钱
Well... okay, fine. I'll kick you a dollar.
不用了  我有钱  谢了
It's okay, I already have a dollar. Thank you, though.
烟友之间
Well, it's just kind of customary
相互给支烟是规矩
to help out a fellow smoker in need.
我感觉你经常跟人借烟吧
I get the sense that you're in need a lot.
你怎么回事
What's your problem?
我没问题啊
I don't have a problem.
有问题的是你  不然也不会跟我墨迹
You do. Otherwise, we wouldn't be having this conversation.
-抱歉打扰了  -本姑娘不计较
- Sorry to bother you. - It's okay.
-我还就抢了  -你不是吧
- Intercepted. - Are you serious?
-贱人  -茶婊
- Bitch! - Bitch.
别紧张  妈妈  苹果酒而已
Relax, Mom. It's only cider.
大家好  我叫奇普·佩莫顿
Hello, everyone. I'm Chip Pemberton.
我就住在那上面
I live right up there.
秉着劳动光荣的精神
In the spirit of Labor Day,
让我们敬真正的劳动人民
let's give it up to the real laborers,
餐宴服务人员们...
the caterers, the valet, and...
-你好啊  -天呐  麦肯齐
- Hey, there. - My God. Mackenzie.
你怎么...  你怎么来了
What are you, wha-what are you doing here?
你邀请我来的
Well, you invited me.
我们每年都邀请你  你从没来过
But we invite you every year and you never come.
-麦肯齐  -克里斯托弗
- Mackenzie, wow. - Christopher.
-有八九年没见了吧...  -我接个电话
- What has it been like, eight, nine years? - Oh, I got to get this.
不  好  好吧...
No, I can't-- okay.
利兹  过来  这是我妹妹  麦肯齐
Liz, look. This is my sister, Mackenzie.
-「传说中」的妹妹吗  -没错
- This is the sister. - Yes.
-「传说中」的妹妹  -是的
- The sister? - Yeah.
你是谁  你是「传说中」的...
What are you? You're the...
-邻居  -邻居
- Neighbor. - The neighbor?
你俩好好叙旧吧  普多[贵妇犬]  打给我
Well, I'll let you two catch up. You don't... Poodle, call me.
「好运」啊
Good luck.
-她叫你普多吗  -很好听吧
- Did she just call you Poodle? - It's cute, right?
-普多吗  -是啊
- Poodle, huh? - Yeah.
-你看起来不错  -谢谢
- You look nice. - Thank you so much.
-你的脸...  你整过了吧  -没错
- What'd you do to your-- you did something to your face? - I did, yeah.
我稍微整了一下
I upgraded a bit.
妈妈  我流鼻血了
Mommy? I got a nosebleed.
-太恶心了  艾尔巴  -我在  普多夫人
- Gross. Get-get-- Alba, could you...? - Yes, Ms. Poodle?
没事  你没事
Okay. Estás bien.
-我们走吧  -谢谢你  艾尔巴
- Vámonos, benito. - Gracias, Alba.
我们去清洗一下
Ay, vamos a limpiar.
两个人说「暗语」呢
They have their own little secret language.
可烦人了
So annoying.
你该见见塞布丽娜
And you should see Sabrina.
她过来了
My-- There she is.
塞布丽娜  这是你的小姨  麦肯齐
Sabrina, look, it's your Aunt Mackenzie.
塞布丽娜
Sabrina.
麦肯齐小姨
Aunt Mackenzie.
你上岁数之后  就没见过你了
I haven't seen you since you were young.
塞布丽娜明年上耶鲁
Sabrina's going to Yale next year.
我被录取了  不代表我就会去
I got into Yale; that doesn't mean I'm going.
-不去也挺好  -你真有趣
- That's probably a good call. - Cute.
你干什么工作来着
Remind me, what do you do again?
你懂我的情况啦
You know how it goes.
什么都干点啦
Just kind of in between things.
-我不懂  但祝你工作顺利  -谢谢
- I don't... but good luck with your things. - Thank you.
-她很出色吧  -是  太「出色」了
- Isn't she amazing?  - She is. I am amazed.
听着  普多  我想给你个机会
So, listen, Yeah? Poodle. I wanted to give you an opportunity
-投资我的未来...  -这就是了
- to invest in my future. - There it is.
-这才是真正的米琪  -你说什么呢
- This is the Mickey that I know. - What are you talking about?
我在你这年纪一半的时候就成家了
I was half your age when I settled down.
什么成家啊  你被有钱佬搞大肚子
Settle down? You got knocked up by some rich guy
当时你是脱衣舞郎
when you were working as a stripper.
我是在脱衣舞俱乐部当服务生
I was waitress at a strip club.
你是个裸上身的服务生
You were a topless waitress.
那更可怜  因为你不会跳舞
And that's even worse; it just means you couldn't dance.
我很会跳舞
I am a great dancer.
联调局
FBI!
我们要以诈欺罪逮捕
We have a warrant for the arrest of Christopher
佩莫顿夫妇
and Pamela Pemberton for fraud.
先查一下那个逃跑的人
Checks the runner at first.
那是谁
Who was that?
不是吧
What?!
小心鞋子
Watch the shoes.
等下  等下
Wait, wait, wait, wait, hang on.
那是我姐
That's my sister.
普多  怎么回事
Poodle! What the hell?
不知道  听着  你今晚得帮我看孩子
Yeah, I don't know. Listen. I need you to watch the kids tonight.
-你家孩子吗  -是
- Your kids? - Yeah.
不  不行  我最不适合带孩子了
No, no, I-I'm a bad choice for that job.
不不  你让他们明早按时上学就行了
No, no. You just need to get them to school in the morning, okay?
整件事就是个误会
This whole thing is a huge misunderstanding.
戴帽子那个邻居呢
Have that neighbor lady, the one with the hat?
绝对不行  我可不放心
Absolutely not. I'd never hear the end of it.
保姆  你们有保姆吧
Babysitter? Don't you have a babysitter?
让五金店外面
I know! Get one of those guys
那些闲人来看孩子吧
outside the hardware store to-to do it. They'll do it.
米琪  我现在没辙了[被铐了]
Mickey. My hands are kind of tied right now.
别整乱我发型啊
Okay, watch the hair.
听着  你就当一天孩子们的小姨
Listen, just act like their aunt for one day
你想要多少钱  我都给
and I'll get you the money that you need, okay?
别把孩子们玩坏了
And don't ruin them!
你们的父母很安全
So... your parents are safe
他们就是想
and they just wanted to see
在事情都解决好之前
if I could spend a little time with you guys
让我多陪陪你们
while this whole thing gets sorted.
会解决的  懂吗
It will get sorted, okay?
等解决完
And when it does,
那些联调局探员就会坐穿牢底了
those FBI pigs will be the ones rotting in jail.
爸爸妈妈坐牢了吗
Mommy and Daddy are in jail?
别担心  本
Don't worry, Ben.
这世道有钱能使鬼推磨
The scales of justice tip in favor of the wealthy.
只要甩他们一脸钱  就搞定了
If we throw enough money at this thing, I'm sure it will go away.
然后我们就以诽谤罪告死他们
And then we'll sue their asses for defamation,
-懂了吗  -懂啦
- okay? - Okay.
这也行
Okay.
我有个主意
So, I have an idea.
不如我们今晚都窝在家里玩扑克吧
Why don't we all just hunker down and play poker all night long,
直到这事都搞定
until this whole thing blows over?
你就别指望我会待在家了
That's not gonna work for me.
我要去参加计划生育的募捐晚宴
Yeah, I'm gonna go to this fund-raiser for Planned Parenthood.
晚上会睡朋友家  明天进城
Probably crash at my friend's place, go to the city tomorrow.
反正我是不着家
So just don't expect to see me too much.
咱俩应该见不着
You know, we probably won't see each other at all.
等再过十年
But hey, let's catch up again
你再来借钱时见吧
in ten years when you need another loan.
听着  塞布丽娜  我指望这事翻身
Listen, Sabrina, I got a lot riding on this gig,
你能不给我
so can you do me a favor
整这些幺蛾子吗
and not be a big, giant, pain in the ass, please?
也许你没文化  不知道
Maybe you don't know this,
计划生育组织
but Planned Parenthood provides
为全国超过三百万女性提供医保吗
health care to over three million women in this country.
小丫头  我很了解计划生育
Sweetie, I know all about Planned Parenthood.
我去过好多次
I should have one of those punch cards
都应该给我积分卡了
that gets you a free sub every ten visits.
真恶心
Gross.
不是...  我是说...  我没...
No, I just meant... I-I never got, like...
就是细菌感染之类的...  总之...
I just had a bunch of bacterial infect-- you know what?
重点是  你想做善事
The point is, you want to make a difference?
就亲身去实践
Go out on the front line, right?
用链子把自己锁在红杉木上  自焚都行
Chain yourself to a redwood, light yourself on fire.
别今晚就行  懂了吗
Just not tonight, understood?
不好意思  我没在听
I'm sorry, were you saying something?
你那个高低眉太搞笑  让我分心了
I was distracted by how uneven your eyebrows are.
我叫的车来了  我要走了
My Uber's here, so I'm out.
-我想回来自然会回来  -好
- I'll be home whenever. - Cool.
你喝什么呢
What are you drinking?
苦艾酒
Just some absinthe.
你想来点吗
Want to take a ride?
说真的吗
Seriously?
你又不开车
You're not driving.
行  那就来吧
Sure, what the hell?
好
Okay.
棒
Yes!
听我说
Listen.
我觉得我们俩开始有点误会
I feel like we got off on the wrong foot,
我知道现在这种情况  你不好受
and I know that you're going through a lot right now,
-你父母...  -我没放在心上
- with your parents and... - I don't care about that.
好吧...
Okay, well,
-不管你在不在乎  -不在乎
- whether you do or you don't... - I don't.
好吧  重点是
All right, well, the point is,
我是你小姨  我想当受欢迎的小姨
I'm your aunt and I want to be the cool aunt.
比如你有男生方面的烦恼会来找我
I want you to come to me with boy problems.
或者女生烦恼  不清楚你的性取向
Or girl problems. I don't assume.
怎么样
What do you say?
我们能重新来过吗  拜托
Can we start over? Please?
行  好吧
Yeah, okay. Why not?
我很高兴咱俩能好好说说话
I just, like, I'm really happy that we're talking,
就是感觉...
and, I don't know, I just feel like...
我有话想跟你说
there is something that I wanted to say to you.
说吧  你可以畅所欲言
Yes, anything, please.
我知道你自以为很聪明
I know you think you're pretty clever
打着小算盘  想把我灌醉
with this little plan to drink me under the table.
但有两个问题
But you see, there are two problems.
你不聪明
You're not.
你也灌不醉本姑娘
And you can't.
我走了  麦肯齐
Peace out, Mackenzie.
你怎么了啊
Something the matter?
我没事  就是突然感觉有点怪
No, I'm good, I just felt kind of funny for a second.
不是吧  怎么怪了
Man. Funny how?
你是说像吃了
Funny like you just drank
六种安眠药那种感觉吗
six different types of sleep medication funny?
什么
What?
你被我下套了  小妞儿
You got straight played, homie.
不  你也喝了  我...
No, but you took it, too.
你就别瞎操心我了  我千杯不醉
I... I don't want you to worry about me. I can handle my 'Quil.
你...  为什么这么做
Why'd you do that?
因为你逃不出我的五指山呗
Because I own you.
-什么  -晚安了  「小公举」  我送你入寝
- What? - Night-night, princess. Let's get you into your jams.
-不要  -来吧
- No. - Come on, I got you.
等下  不是吧  等下
No, wait! Wait. Hold on.
钥匙  艾尔巴
Keys. Alba.
给我车钥匙  孩子们要迟到了
I need some car keys, the kids are late.
他们已经上学了
The kids go to school already.
普多夫人平时会睡过头
Ms. Poodle likes to sleep in, too,
都是我来搞定
so I took care of it.
真简单
That was easy.
你想让我给你做早餐吗
You want me to make you breakfast?
你想要做  我也不拦你啊
Well, I mean, I don't want you to not make me breakfast.
好吧  那个泳池  水能加热吗
All right, so what's the deal with that pool? Is it heated?
我不知道  我没试过
I don't know. I never tried.
你每天为这个家尽心尽力
You're telling me you're here every single day busting your hump,
这些自命不凡的有钱佬都没让你享受下泳池吗
these entitled monkeys don't even let you get wet?
-我不会游泳  -这不是重点
- I cannot swim. - That's not the point.
泳池就是个比喻
The pool's a metaphor.
这样太不厚道了  这样不对
No, you're getting boxed out, and I don't like that.
这样吧
I'll tell you what,
只要我在这儿  咱俩就平起平坐
as long as I'm here, you and me, we're equals.
-可以吗  -当然了
- Yeah? - Yeah, in fact...
来吧  拉张椅子  我们一起吃早饭
pull up a chair, we're eating breakfast together.
可以吗
Really?
好吧
Okay.
等下  等下
Wait, wait, wait.
你得先做早饭啊
I mean... you got to cook the food first.
做完饭之后  就不分主仆
But after that, equals.
-这件应该很有意思  -好
- Yeah, that one'll be fun. - Okay.
还有鞋
Here come the shoes.
靠近点  我碰不到  信我
Come closer, I can't reach it. Trust me.
-不  -别这样
- No! - Come on!
天呐  太扫兴啦
Man. You are a bummer.
-接球  -我不想
- Catch it! - What? I don't want it.
她怎么了
What's the matter with her?
我觉得她死了
I think she's dead.
她没死  还喘着气呢
She's not dead, I can see her breathing.
你们放学啦
You guys are home.
不错
Cool.
晚上想吃什么
What's everybody thinking for dinner?
我们刚吃完早饭呀
We just ate breakfast.
我们昨天放学后回来  就见你躺在这儿了
You were like this when we came home from school yesterday.
艾尔巴呢
Well, where's Alba?
救命啊
Help!
救我啊
Somebody!
好吧...  早上好
All right, well... good morning.
你头上戴了个什么玩意儿
What's that crap on your head?
猫头鹰  是我们的吉祥物
An owl, it's our mascot.
我们今天要见到一只活的了
We're unveiling a live one today at assembly.
肯定好玩极了
It's gonna be awesome.
根本不是  而是很变态
It's not gonna be awesome, it's sick.
猫头鹰会困在笼子里
He's gonna be trapped in a cage
一群讨厌的蠢孩子会戳他  喂他吃软糖
while a bunch of morons poke him and feed him gummy bears.
这张专辑太逊了  「破歌」真难听
Change the record. This song sucks.
要是有人
How would you feel
把你拉走强制关到笼子里呢
if someone ripped you off your barstool and threw you in a cage?
我被关的次数
I cannot count the number of times
都多到数不清了
I've been ripped off a barstool and thrown in a cage.
故事「感人」
Cool story.
我们要走了
We're gonna head out, okay?
跟新郎问好吧
Give my regards to the groom.
不如我送你们去学校吧
How about I drive you guys?
我还是离开这里吧
Should probably get out of the house.
昨天有点玩过头了
Yesterday kind of got away from me.
可恶  该死...  好了
Get in there, you bastard. Let's do it.
好  我们到了
There. Here we are.
再见  塞布丽娜  今天过得愉快哦
Bye, Sabrina. Have a great day.
我爱你  小姨爱你哦
I love you. Auntie loves you all day long.
早  奇普
Morning, Chip.
早  小黛
Hey, Steffi.
-最近好吗...  -你好啊  「小奇普」
- How's it going? - 'Sup, Chippy?
父母坐牢坐得舒服吗
How are your folks liking the clink?
混蛋奇诺·皮尼罗
Freaking Geno Pinero!
我讨厌死他了
I hate that guy.
那你就反抗啊
Yeah. Well, do something about it.
怎么反抗
Like what?
那家伙就是个神经病
The guy is a maniac.
他把水管捅进丹尼的屁股
He stuck a garden hose up Danny Clerkin's butt
水从鼻子涌出来了
and the water shot out of his nose!
好吧  那不是真的
Okay. Well, that didn't happen,
但还有这样的传闻  挺有意思
but I am delighted that the rumor exists.
小子  下次他再欺负你
Look, pal, next time he gives you crap,
你就拽下他的裤子
yank his pants down
嘲笑他的鸡鸡小
and point at his tiny pecker.
-那样就行了  -你也不正常
- That'll do it. - You're insane, okay?
他会揍死我
He-He'll pound me.
不会  「搞笑」分分钟虐死「暴力」
No! Humor trumps violence.
信我  女生喜欢风趣搞笑的男生
Trust me, girls want the funny guy.
麦肯齐
Mackenzie.
我就感觉像你
I thought that was you.
我叫利兹  你姐的朋友
Liz, Poodle's friend.
孩子带得怎么样啊
How are you managing with the kids?
塞布丽娜有些难搞哦
Sabrina can be a bit of a handful.
塞布丽娜吗  她可帮忙了
Sabrina? No, she's been very helpful.
没有她  我都不知道该怎么办
I don't know how I'd manage without her.
我得走了
Well, I got to run.
你该休息一下  你看上去筋疲力尽
Make sure you get some sleep, you look tired.
-再见哦  亲  -再见  亲
- Bye, hon. - Bye, hon.
只有周二才能够应付那种婊气的女人啊
That woman is a real see you next Tuesday.
周二怎么了
What happens on Tuesday?
墨西哥卷饼  两元特惠酒饮
Tacos. Two-dollar drink specials.
你怎么还不去上课
What are you still doing there?
我想念爸爸和妈妈
I miss Mommy and Daddy.
好吧  这样吧  小家伙
Well... I'll tell you what, kid.
坐到前面吧
Why don't you pop on up front?
你今天翘课吧  来吧
You are playing hooky today. Come on.
但如果我错过了重要课程内容呢
But what if I miss something important?
能错过什么
Like what?
怎么把鼻屎磋没吗
How to roll your boogers between your fingers till they disappear?
坐稳了
Buckle up.
宿醉太难受了
I am hungover.
什么是宿醉
What's hungover?
就是...
Well, you know, it's, like...
比如你吃了很多糖果
you know when you eat a whole bunch of candy?
很多甜食  吃的时候感觉很美好
Sweet stuff, and at the time it feels great,
但第二天会肚子痛
but then the next day you got, like, a tummy ache?
这就是「宿醉」的感觉
That's hungover.
你试过上大号吗
Have you tried pooping?
有时候拉完  就好受了
Sometimes that makes my tummy feel better.
我没有
I have not. But I will definitely
但我会考虑一下这么做  谢谢
take that into consideration. Thank you.
本  你饿吗
Ben, you hungry?
想吃冰淇淋吗
You, feeling like having some ice cream?
我不能吃  我妈说我对冰淇淋过敏
I can't. My mom says I'm allergic.
我告诉你实话吧
Yeah, well, I got news for you, pal.
你妈就是把她的饮食失调症加之于你了
Your mom is just projecting her own eating disorders onto you.
什么是「加之于你」
What's projecting?
问得好  意思就是...
Great question. Projecting, that's, like,
明明是自己的问题
when something's wrong with you,
-你却觉得别人有问题  -起火了
- but you think something's wrong with somebody else. - Fire!
-怎么了  怎么了  -救火啊
- What? What? Fire! - Help!
是啊  起火了  快灭火
Yeah. Somebody get that.
来吧  小家伙  吃吧
Here you go, buddy, dig in.
为什么不花钱买呢
Why didn't we pay for it?
我没钱呗
I don't have any money.
为什么呢
Why not?
-有些人就比别人穷呗  -为什么呢
- Some people have less money than others. - Why?
小家伙  我不会花一整天时间
Look, pal. I'm not gonna just stop the whole day and explain
跟你解释经济收入这回事
the ins and outs of the economy to you, all right, now?
因为很没劲...  懂吗
'Cause it's boring, okay?
还因为我其实也不是很懂
And also 'cause I don't totally have a firm grasp on it myself.
我可以给你买呀
Well, I would have paid for you.
你真是「暖男」
You are so sweet.
不如我来背你...  那是...
Now, don't you go breaking your piggy bank open.
那是运通黑卡吗
Is that... is that a Black Card?
塞布丽娜
Sabrina?
你好啊
What's up?
你怎么把这破鸟弄到家里来了
What is that gross bird doing in this house?
我从学校偷回来的
I stole him from school.
我实在不忍心看鸟儿这样被对待
I just couldn't watch him be treated like that anymore, you know?
是啊  这鸟在这里跟你那些蠢朋友
Yes. Yes. I'm sure he's much happier here
一起听着破曲  肯定快活多了
listening to thumping techno with your moron friends.
-管好你这只鸟  -别激动
- Control your animal! - Relax.
我要将这只猫头鹰送到野生保护地放生
I'm gonna liberate him in a wildlife preserve near Stratford.
你脑子进水了啊
Are you insane?
被人抓到之前  赶紧还回学校
Take him back to school right this second, before you get busted.
这下好了
Great!
你又怎么了
What happened to you?
我告诉你怎么了
I'll tell you what happened.
我想用「搞笑」虐死「暴力」
I tried to trump violence with humor,
结果我被「暴力」虐惨了
and violence won by a landslide.
显然你做得不对啊
Well, clearly you didn't do it right.
你有嘲笑他的鸡鸡小吗
Did you remember to laugh at his tiny penis?
这部分才是亮点
That part's pretty important.
超级大  没被他的「大雕」打就不错了
It was humongous! I'm lucky he didn't beat me with it.
你去处理一下脸上的伤吧
Okay. I... uh, go put a steak on your face or something, I don't know.
塞布丽娜  你能用下脑子吗
Sabrina, can you please try and think for a second?
是你教我  做善事就要亲身去实践
You're the one who told me to get out on the front lines.
我教的都是馊招  大家都知道
Well, I don't... I give terrible advice! Everybody knows that.
看看我多惨啊
Look at me! I'm grotesque.
-我要告死他  -什么罪名
- I'm gonna sue his ass. - For what?
殴打
Battery.
然后我要告学校失职
And then I'm going to sue the school for negligence.
得了吧
Okay. Pipe down, all right?
告死别人  也俘获不了那女孩的芳心
You're not gonna sue your way into this girl's pants.
是吗  那你就瞧着吧
Yeah? Watch me!
又怎么了
Now what?
你有什么事啊
What do you want?
就是过来看看
Just checking in.
我感觉你不会做饭
You don't strike me as much of a cook,
所以我做了点炖锅菜给你
so I brought you a casserole.
你真是个大好人啊
You are so, so sweet.
糟糕了...
Shoot.
你是故意的
You did that on purpose.
天呐...  你把他怎么了
My, what did you do to him?
不是我打的
No. I didn't do that.
他在学校看同学的小鸡鸡  被揍了
He got pounded at school for checking out some kid's wiener.
都是拜你所赐
Because of you!
现在小黛觉得我就是怂货
Now Steffi thinks I'm a joke
学校里的人都知道奇诺有个「大雕」了
and Geno's got the raddest freaking dong in school.
米琪小姨  能再给我点冰淇淋吗
Mickey, can I have some more ice cream?
忍不了了  我要报警
That's it. I'm calling the cops.
回你自己家报警吧
Why don't you call the cops from your house?
你别碰我
Get your hands off me.
我还没使劲呢
Lady, I haven't even begun to put hands on you.
两位女士  下午好
Afternoon, ladies.
-又是你  -一切都好吧
- You again. - Is everything okay?
警官  这个女人对我动粗了
Officer, this woman assaulted me.
第一  这种指控太荒唐
Number one, that is ludicrous.
第二  这人根本算不上警察
Number two, this man is an officer of nothing.
-孩子们跟她在一起不安全  -孩子们很好
- She's a danger to these children. - The kids are fine.
他们看起来可不好啊
They do not look fine.
-你俩都滚出我家  -这不是你家
You know what? Why don't you both get out of my house? It's not your house.
-你有身份证明吗  -给你看  做梦吧
- Can I see some identification? - I'm not showing you dick.
塞布丽娜  你别走  我还没跟你谈完
Sabrina? Don't you go anywhere. I am not done talking to you.
-你住在这里吗  -是的
- Do you live here? - Yeah.
这个人是谁
Who is this?
不认识
No idea.
女士  请你出来  我们查明一下
Okay, ma'am. Why don't we step outside until we figure this out?
你都不是个真警察  戴个假警章吓唬谁啊
You are not even a real cop. You've got a cloth badge.
别逼我动手
Don't make me detain you.
怎么制服我啊  你都没有枪
With what? You have no gun.
是  但我有电击枪
No, I have a Taser.
小贱人  希望你带了两把
Bitch, I hope you brought two,
电击对姐来说  就跟过家家似的
'cause Mama's got a real high tolerance.
好吧  你逼我的
Okay. Here we go.
天呐  不
No!
我的天呐  太抱歉了
My God, I'm so sorry!
-你没事吧  -看着不像没事
- Are you okay? - I doubt it.
这都是你的错  我要找真警察了
This is all your fault. I'm calling the real police for this...
艾尔巴  你来真格的啊
Alba! Are you serious?
太给力了
That was unbelievable.
我不喜欢这些人  但我喜欢你
I don't like these people, but I like you.
你去阻止塞布丽娜吧
So, go stop Sabrina,
别担心  我会「料理」好他们
and don't worry, I will clean this up.
好  好
Y-Yeah. Yeah.
多嘴问一下  你说「料理」是指...
Just to be clear, when you say clean it up...?
我把他们安全送回家
I take 'em home, make sure they're okay.
好  这就好  谢谢
Okay. Good, good, good. Thank you!
塞布丽娜  是我
Sabrina, it's me!
你给我听着  你不能偷猫头鹰
Listen to me, you can't just steal owls.
如果你将其放生
If you free this owl,
我就再找一只弄死  「以牙还牙」
I will murder another one, just to even the score.
你可听好了
So, know that!
听到留言  就给我回电
This is an insane message. Call me back.
塞布丽娜  你在哪儿
Sabrina, where are you?!
塞布丽娜  你没事吧
Sabrina, are you okay?
我没事啊  我在索霍区的阁楼派对上呢
Yeah, I'm cool. I'm at this loft party in SoHo.
我没事
It's all right.
那我来野生动物保护区干什么
Then what am I doing at the wildlife preserve?
打开后备箱
Pop the trunk.
不  本  把火柴给我
No, Ben. Give me the matches.
别乱翻我包  好吗
Please stay out of my purse, okay?
-喂  -妹妹  是我
- Hello. - Hey, sis, it's me.
你跑哪去了
Where the hell are you?
我们不得不逃出境了
We had to flee the country.
啥
What?
你不是说只是一场误会吗
I thought you said it was a misunderstanding.
本来是  就是
It was. It is.
-那...  -这事很复杂  听着
- Well... - It's complicated. Listen.
你得帮我多照顾一段时间孩子们了
I need you to watch the kids a little longer.
不行  不行  不行
No. No. Nope.
我才不要  我已经「坐过牢」了
No, I'm not gonna do that. I already did my time.
不行  我不答应
No, my answer's no.
-抱歉  手机信号不好...  -才不是
- Sorry, Mick, no, yeah, you-you're breaking up. - No...
-我听不清...   -不不不  别给我整这套
- I can't hear you. - No, no, no. I know what you're doing.
别装了  我听得清  得了吧  不行  普多
Stop it. I can hear you just fine. No, Poodle.
-告诉孩子们  妈妈爱他们  -不行
- Tell the kids Mommy loves them. - No.
-我很快回来  -普多  不行
- I'll be back soon. All right. - Poodle, no!
-听不清了...  -你挂我电话试试
- Can't hear you, hanging up, gotta go. - Don't you hang up the phone.
喂  喂
Hello? Hello?
你没事吧
You okay?
你看起来不怎么样啊
You don't look so hot.
你一直都是一副衰相  但...
I mean, you never look great, but
你现在的样子更衰
right now you look, like, actively bad.
我没事  塞布丽娜  多谢关心
No. I'm fine, Sabrina. Thank you for your concern.
-你怎么样  -我感觉好极了
- How are you? - I'm awesome.
这鸡肉真好吃
This chicken is fantastic.
亲爱的  那可不是鸡肉
Sweetheart. That's not chicken.